OLUWATOSIN FAJINMI

linkedin.com/in/oluwatosin-fajinmi Lagos, Nigeria 08024087183 tosin.tope81@gmail.com

A Customer-oriented Sales Specialist, armed with innate skills and knowledge with a strong history of leading high-performance teams to meet or exceed objectives. Demonstrates knowledge and experience in daily customer interphase as well as consistently meeting deadlines and increasing company revenue. Possess an award of Best Sales Agent, Diploma in Customer Relationship Management and Certification of Fundamental of Digital Marketing.

EXPERIENCE

YOUVERIFY INC.

BUSINESS DEVELOPMENT EXECUTIVE | Aug 2020 - Present

- Oversee the sales process to attract new clients.
- Work with team members to identify and manage risks.
- Maintain fruitful relationships with clients and address their needs effectively.
- Research and identify new market opportunities.
- Prepare and deliver pitches to potential customers.
- Planning and overseeing new marketing initiatives.
- Follow company guidelines and procedures for acquisition of customers, submission of tenders.
- Collaborating with management on sales goals, planning, and forecasting; maintaining short- and long-term business development plans.
- Drafting business proposals and contracts to draw more revenue from clients.
- Foster a collaborative environment within the organization.
- Maintain knowledge of all product and service offered by the company.
- Ability to use CRM(customer relationship management) systems to effectively execute multiple responsibilities and deliverables.

PAGE FINANCIAL INTERNATIONAL SERVICES, Lagos

TELE-SALES ASSOCIATE | Jan 2018 - Dec 2019

- Increasing and exceeding monthly targets.
- Making over 50 outbound calls daily in order to promote company products and services.
- Prospecting on daily basis, calling from prospect list provided by customer Marketing, referrals and by researching possible new customers.
- Supervised team of seven staff members.
- Met performance targets in all areas such as speed, accuracy, volume, satisfaction, and issue resolution.

PLEDGE FINANCE/ PAGE FINANCIAL SERVICES

Telesales Associate | Jan 2018 - Jan 2019

- Over 100% YTD achieved individually 2018 Pledge/Page Financial Services Limited.
- Increasing and exceeding monthly targets.
- Making over 50 outbound calls daily in order to promote company products and services.
- Prospecting on daily basis, calling from prospect list provided by customer ,Marketing, referrals and by researching possible new customers.

RENMONEY MFB, Lagos

SALES EXECUTIVE | Feb 2016 - Dec 2017

- Increasing and exceeding New To Bank(NTB) customers base target.
- Increased sales by 100% over the year for the team.
- Responsible for Personal Lending to prospective clients.
- Prospecting for new cooperate companies and converting them to Loan at-work customers.

- Valuate, analyze and recommend loan for final approval.
- Processing and first level underwriting on loan applications.
- Qualified prospects to determine potential for future sales and prioritize conversion efforts.

TRANSMISSION COMPANY OF NIGERIA

FIELD ENGINEER | Jan 2015 - Jan 2016

- Installation, commissioning and maintenance of LV/MV/HV transformers.
- Data collation and analysis of system performance of Lagos region 330/132kv transmission network.
- Testing and commissioning of protection and control applications, scheme and equipment such as power transformers and relays to ascertain and confirm their reliability, sensitivity and speed of operation.
- Performing other related duties as needed upon request by immediate supervisor.

XHS NIGERIA, Lagos

INTERN | Jan 2012 - Jan 2013

- Responsible for maintaining electrical installation & networking cables.
- Working closely with a team of engineers, installers and supervisors.
- Assisting on power planning and implementation.
- Working on documentation and capacity management.
- Identifying problems and then suggesting technical engineering solutions.

EDUCATION

LADOKE AKINTOLA UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY

Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech) Electrical/Electronics Engineering (Apr 2014)

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- Customer service skills
- Sales Strategy
- Networking
- Team Leadership
- Business Development
- Communication skills
- Lead Nurturing
- Team Management
- Relationship Management
- Market Research
- Problem Solving
- Strategic Planning
- Customer Relationship Management

CERTIFICATIONS

- Diploma in Customer Relationship Management
- The Fundamentals of Digital Marketing